const qnaData = [
    {
        id: 1,
        eventKey: "0",
        question: "How do I make a purchase with Eyeviser?",
        answer: `
        Step 1: Find out what frames and lenses are suited for your face shape and lifestyle.
        Take a look at our lens guide and frames guide to find out which lens type and frame shape best suit you. 
        If you’re pressed for time, feel free to use our lens selector tool or frame selector tool to help you decide.  
        If you prefer advice from our expert, ping us via the Facebook messaging icon or whatsapp 88501568.

        Step 2: Choose the option that suits you best!
        1) Home: eye test and eyewear at your doorstep
        Perfect for those who:
        prefer not to go outside to minimise exposure to Covid-19,
        appreciate the convenience of testing your eyes and fitting eyeglasses at home with your family,
        have family members with limited mobility, or feel more at ease fitting eyewear at home
        ** Note for children below 12, the first comprehensive eye examination for kids should be done in-store
        How it works:
        Our optometrist will visit your house to do a refraction, let you try on frames and fit your eyeglasses.
        Eyewear will be delivered straight to your doorstep

        2) In-store: eye test in store
        Perfect for those who:
        Prefer doing the eye test outside of their home or it’s inconvenient for us to go down to your home to do the testing,
        Want to minimise the time spent in stores to minimise exposure to Covid-19
        How it works:
        Visit the store for the eye test
        Share your prescription with us
        We can meet you at a location of your choice to let you try on frames and fit your eyeglasses.
        Eyewear will be delivered straight to your doorstep


        3) Virtual: no eye test needed
        Perfect for those who:
        Have an existing valid prescription.
        Are 16 and above, not have any organic eye disease or systemic medical condition that will affect vision
        and require only spectacles for single vision use, with power up to ±6.00D/ -2.00DC. 
        (i.e. no prism, curve lenses, progressive lenses, bifocal lenses or free-form single vision lens).
        How it works:
        Schedule a free virtual consultation with our optometrist who will do history-taking and confirm you are eligible for this virtual option.
        We can meet you at a location of your choice to let you try on frames and fit your eyeglasses, or you can choose your frames online.
        Eyewear will be delivered straight to your doorstep. We can adjust your frame if it doesn’t fit.        
        `
        
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        eventKey: "1",
        question: "What happens if I need to adjust my glasses or need after-sales service?",
        answer: "For every purchase of Signature eyewear, we will visit you at your preferred location to adjust your frames or replace your nosepads, at no additional charge."
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        eventKey: "2",
        question: "When can I expect to receive my glasses?",
        answer: "The lead time between each eyeglass order may vary according to stock availability. Generally, you can expect the product to reach you in about 7 to 10 days from the day we receive your up-to-date prescription."
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        eventKey: "3",
        question: "Do you ship your products outside of Singapore?",
        answer: "Yes, we ship internationally. Do contact us for more details on the shipping fees and expected delivery time."
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        eventKey: "4",
        question: "How much do I have to pay for shipping? Is it free?",
        answer: "Spend above $150 in one order to enjoy free shipping from us! Otherwise, a flat shipping fee of SGD $4 will apply."
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        eventKey: "5",
        question: "What does the one-year lens warranty cover?",
        answer: "At My Eye Matters, your satisfaction is our priority. Our Signature series offers a one-year lens warranty against manufacturing defects. Do note that the replacement of lens will only be given where due care has been exercised by the wearer."
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        eventKey: "6",
        question: "Am I allowed to request for a product refund or exchange?",
        answer: "Each pair of eyeglasses is customised to your prescription. Due to personal and hygienic reasons, it is unfortunately not possible to return the eyeglasses once the item has been delivered. There will also be no refund or exchanges made in the event that an incorrect prescription was submitted.  To minimise errors, we will contact you before processing the eyeglasses to make sure you selected the right frame, colour and have an up-to-date prescription."
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        eventKey: "7",
        question: "How do the frames and lenses at My Eye Matters compare with other brands?",
        answer: "Our frames have the quality of a European CE mark and are made by the same manufacturers that make branded frames that cost many times more.  All lenses under our Signature Series are anti-reflection, water, smudge, scratch and dust resistant and provide all-round UV protection.  All are from established international brands handpicked by industry experts as the best in class. If you have a tight budget and prefer lenses without the features in our Signature Series, please contact us for alternative options (though we strongly advise against it, because your eyes matter, and deserve the best protection)."
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        eventKey: "8",
        question: "How do I know if a certain frame and/or lens is suitable for me?",
        answer: `Don’t worry— we’ve got your back! You can find out which lens are best suited to your lifestyle by using our lens selector tool.
        We also have a frame selector tool to help pick out the best frames for your face shape.
        `
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        eventKey: "9",
        question: "What is the right way to care for my glasses?",
        answer: `
        DOs:
        Use the microfibre cloth provided with the eyewear to wipe your lenses.  
        Use two hands to take off and put on your glasses. Wearing and removing your eyeglass single-handedly can place unnecessary strain on the hinges, leading to your frame to bend or break easily.
        Store your eyeglasses in a carrying case when not in use. 

        DO NOTs:
        Use tissue paper, the hem of your shirt or a handkerchief to wipe your eyeglass. Minute scratches to the lens can result.
        Keep your eyeglass in a position with its lens facing downwards. It is highly likely for your lens to get scratched when left exposed to a surface. 
        `
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        eventKey: "10",
        question: "What happens if I submit the wrong order form?",
        answer: "We reach out to every customer individually after an order is placed. In the event that you have submitted your order inaccurately, simply let us know when we contact you or email us at hello@myeyematters.com."
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        eventKey: "11",
        question: "How do I know if I need a new prescription?",
        answer: "You can take an online visual acuity test with your eyewear on to give you a preliminary indication of whether they are still suitable. However, we strongly recommend that you take an eye exam in store if you haven’t taken one in the last year to have an up-to-date prescription and confirm that you do not have any underlying conditions that could affect your vision. "
    }
]

export default qnaData;